////////////////////////////798B Strings///////////////////////////////////////
//////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
{
B. Mike and strings
time limit per test2 seconds
memory limit per test256 megabytes
inputstandard input
outputstandard output
Mike has n strings s1, s2, ..., sn each consisting of lowercase English letters. 
In one move he can choose a string si, erase the first character and append it to the end of the string.
 For example, if he has the string "coolmike", in one move he can transform it into the string "oolmikec".

Now Mike asks himself: what is minimal number of moves that he needs to do in order to make all the strings equal?

Input
The first line contains integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 50) — the number of strings.

This is followed by n lines which contain a string each. The i-th line corresponding to string si. 
Lengths of strings are equal. Lengths of each string is positive and don't exceed 50.

Output
Print the minimal number of moves Mike needs in order to make all the strings equal or print  - 1 
if there is no solution.

Examples
input
4
xzzwo
zwoxz
zzwox
xzzwo
output
5
input
2
molzv
lzvmo
output
2
input
3
kc
kc
kc
output
0
input
3
aa
aa
ab
output
-1
Note
In the first sample testcase the optimal scenario is to perform operations in such a way
 as to transform all strings into "zwoxz".

}
////////////////////////////817B Minimum i j k/////////////////////////////////
//////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
B. Makes And The Product
time limit per test2 seconds
memory limit per test256 megabytes
inputstandard input
outputstandard output
After returning from the army Makes received a gift — an array a consisting of n positive
 integer numbers.
 He hadn't been solving problems for a long time, so he became interested to answer a particular question:
 how many triples of indices (i,  j,  k) (i < j < k), such that ai·aj·ak is minimum possible, are there in the array? 
Help him with it!

Input
The first line of input contains a positive integer number n (3 ≤ n ≤ 105) — the number 
of elements in array a.
 The second line contains n positive integer numbers ai (1 ≤ ai ≤ 109) — the elements of a given array.

Output
Print one number — the quantity of triples (i,  j,  k) such that i,  j and k 
are pairwise distinct and ai·aj·ak is minimum possible.

Examples
input
4
1 1 1 1
output
4
input
5
1 3 2 3 4
output
2
input
6
1 3 3 1 3 2
output
1
Note
In the first example Makes always chooses three ones out of four, and the number of ways to choose them is 4.

In the second example a triple of numbers (1, 2, 3) is chosen (numbers, not indices). 
Since there are two ways to choose an element 3, then the answer is 2.

In the third example a triple of numbers (1, 1, 2) is chosen, and there's only one way to choose indices.

////////////////////////////821A Laboratory////////////////////////////////////
//////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////

A. Okabe and Future Gadget Laboratory
time limit per test2 seconds
memory limit per test256 megabytes
inputstandard input
outputstandard output
Okabe needs to renovate the Future Gadget Laboratory after he tried doing some crazy experiments!
 The lab is represented as an n by n square grid of integers. 
A good lab is defined as a lab in which every number not equal to 1 can be expressed
 as the sum of a number in the same row and a number in the same column. In other words,
 for every x, y such that 1 ≤ x, y ≤ n and ax, y ≠ 1, there should exist two 
indices s and t so that ax, y = ax, s + at, y, where ai, j denotes the integer in i-th row and j-th column.

Help Okabe determine whether a given lab is good!

Input
The first line of input contains the integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 50) — the size of the lab.

The next n lines contain n space-separated integers denoting a row of the grid.
 The j-th integer in the i-th row is ai, j (1 ≤ ai, j ≤ 105).

Output
Print "Yes" if the given lab is good and "No" otherwise.

You can output each letter in upper or lower case.

Examples
input
3
1 1 2
2 3 1
6 4 1
output
Yes
input
3
1 5 2
1 1 1
1 2 3
output
No
Note
In the first sample test, the 6 in the bottom left corner is valid because 
it is the sum of the 2 above it and the 4 on the right.
 The same holds for every number not equal to 1 in this table, so the answer is "Yes".

In the second sample test, the 5 cannot be formed as the sum of an integer in the same row
 and an integer in the same column. Thus the answer is "No".
////////////////////////////834A Spinner///////////////////////////////////////
//////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
A. The Useless Toy
time limit per test1 second
memory limit per test256 megabytes
inputstandard input
outputstandard output

Walking through the streets of Marshmallow City, Slastyona have spotted some merchants selling 
a kind of useless toy which is very popular nowadays – caramel spinner!
 Wanting to join the craze, she has immediately bought the strange contraption.

Spinners in Sweetland have the form of V-shaped pieces of caramel. Each spinner can, 
well, spin around an invisible magic axis. At a specific point in time, 
a spinner can take 4 positions shown below (each one rotated 90 degrees relative to the previous,
 with the fourth one followed by the first one):


After the spinner was spun, it starts its rotation, which is described by a following algorithm:
 the spinner maintains its position for a second then majestically switches to the next position 
in clockwise or counter-clockwise order, depending on the direction the spinner was spun in.

Slastyona managed to have spinner rotating for exactly n seconds. Being fascinated by elegance of the process,
 she completely forgot the direction the spinner was spun in! 
Lucky for her, she managed to recall the starting position, and wants to deduct the direction given
 the information she knows. Help her do this.

Input
There are two characters in the first string – the starting and the ending position of a spinner.
 The position is encoded with one of the following characters: v (ASCII code 118, lowercase v), 
< (ASCII code 60), ^ (ASCII code 94) or > (ASCII code 62) (see the picture above for reference).
 Characters are separated by a single space.

In the second strings, a single number n is given (0 ≤ n ≤ 109) – the duration of the rotation.

It is guaranteed that the ending position of a spinner is a result of a n second spin in any of the directions,
 assuming the given starting position.

Output
Output cw, if the direction is clockwise, ccw – if counter-clockwise, and undefined otherwise.

Examples
input
^ >
1
output
cw
input
< ^
3
output
ccw
input
^ v
6
output
undefined


////////////////////////////799A Cakes Baking Optimization////////////////////
//////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////

A. Carrot Cakes
time limit per test1 second
memory limit per test256 megabytes
inputstandard input
outputstandard output
In some game by Playrix it takes t minutes for an oven to bake k carrot cakes,
 all cakes are ready at the same moment t minutes after they started baking.
 Arkady needs at least n cakes to complete a task, but he currently don't have any.
 However, he has infinitely many ingredients and one oven. Moreover,
 Arkady can build one more similar oven to make the process faster, it would take d minutes 
to build the oven. While the new oven is being built, only old one can bake cakes, after the new oven
 is built, both ovens bake simultaneously. Arkady can't build more than one oven.

Determine if it is reasonable to build the second oven, i.e. will it decrease 
the minimum time needed to get n cakes or not. If the time needed with the second oven is the same as with one oven,
 then it is unreasonable.

Input
The only line contains four integers n, t, k, d (1 ≤ n, t, k, d ≤ 1 000) — the number of cakes needed, 
the time needed for one oven to bake k cakes, the number of cakes baked at the same time,
 the time needed to build the second oven.

Output
If it is reasonable to build the second oven, print "YES". Otherwise print "NO".

Examples
input
8 6 4 5
output
YES
input
8 6 4 6
output
NO
input
10 3 11 4
output
NO
input
4 2 1 4
output
YES
Note
In the first example it is possible to get 8 cakes in 12 minutes using one oven.
 The second oven can be built in 5 minutes, so after 6 minutes the first oven bakes 4 cakes,
 the second oven bakes 4 more ovens after 11 minutes. Thus, it is reasonable to build the second oven.

In the second example it doesn't matter whether we build the second oven or not, 
thus it takes 12 minutes to bake 8 cakes in both cases. Thus, it is unreasonable to build the second oven.

In the third example the first oven bakes 11 cakes in 3 minutes,
 that is more than needed 10. It is unreasonable to build the second oven,
 because its building takes more time that baking the needed number of cakes using the only oven.


////////////////////////////828A Restaurant////////////////////////////////////
//////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
A. Restaurant Tables
time limit per test1 second
memory limit per test256 megabytes
inputstandard input
outputstandard output
In a small restaurant there are a tables for one person and b tables for two persons.

It it known that n groups of people come today, each consisting of one or two people.

If a group consist of one person, it is seated at a vacant one-seater table.
 If there are none of them, it is seated at a vacant two-seater table. 
If there are none of them, it is seated at a two-seater table occupied by single person.
 If there are still none of them, the restaurant denies service to this group.

If a group consist of two people, it is seated at a vacant two-seater table.
 If there are none of them, the restaurant denies service to this group.

You are given a chronological order of groups coming.
 You are to determine the total number of people the restaurant denies service to.

Input
The first line contains three integers n, a and b (1 ≤ n ≤ 2·105, 1 ≤ a, b ≤ 2·105) — the number of groups
 coming to the restaurant, the number of one-seater and the number of two-seater tables.

The second line contains a sequence of integers t1, t2, ..., tn (1 ≤ ti ≤ 2) — the description
 of clients in chronological order. 
If ti is equal to one, then the i-th group consists of one person, otherwise the i-th group consists of two people.

Output
Print the total number of people the restaurant denies service to.

Examples
input
4 1 2
1 2 1 1
output
0
input
4 1 1
1 1 2 1
output
2
Note
In the first example the first group consists of one person,
 it is seated at a vacant one-seater table.
 The next group occupies a whole two-seater table. 
The third group consists of one person, it occupies one place at the remaining two-seater table.
 The fourth group consists of one person, he is seated at the remaining seat at the two-seater table. 
Thus, all clients are served.

In the second example the first group consists of one person,
 it is seated at the vacant one-seater table. 
The next group consists of one person, it occupies one place at the two-seater table.
 It's impossible to seat the next group of two people, so the restaurant denies service to them. 
The fourth group consists of one person, he is seated at the remaining seat at the two-seater table. 
Thus, the restaurant denies service to 2 clients.



////////////////////////////831A Unimodal Array////////////////////////////////
//////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////

A. Unimodal Array
time limit per test1 second
memory limit per test256 megabytes
inputstandard input
outputstandard output
Array of integers is unimodal, if:

it is strictly increasing in the beginning;
after that it is constant;
after that it is strictly decreasing.
The first block (increasing) and the last block (decreasing) may be absent.
 It is allowed that both of this blocks are absent.

For example, the following three arrays are unimodal: [5, 7, 11, 11, 2, 1], [4, 4, 2], [7], 
but the following three are not unimodal: [5, 5, 6, 6, 1], [1, 2, 1, 2], [4, 5, 5, 6].

Write a program that checks if an array is unimodal.

Input
The first line contains integer n (1 ≤ n ≤ 100) — the number of elements in the array.

The second line contains n integers a1, a2, ..., an (1 ≤ ai ≤ 1 000) — the elements of the array.

Output
Print "YES" if the given array is unimodal. Otherwise, print "NO".

You can output each letter in any case (upper or lower).

Examples
input
6
1 5 5 5 4 2
output
YES
input
5
10 20 30 20 10
output
YES
input
4
1 2 1 2
output
NO
input
7
3 3 3 3 3 3 3
output
YES
Note
In the first example the array is unimodal, because it is strictly increasing in the beginning (from position 1 to position 2, inclusively), that it is constant (from position 2 to position 4, inclusively) and then it is strictly decreasing (from position 4 to position 6, inclusively).


////////////////////////////825A Binary Protocol///////////////////////////////
//////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
A. Binary Protocol
time limit per test1 second
memory limit per test256 megabytes
inputstandard input
outputstandard output
Polycarp has just invented a new binary protocol for data transmission. 
He is encoding positive integer decimal number to binary string using following algorithm:

Each digit is represented with number of '1' characters equal to the value of that digit (for 0 it is zero ones).
Digits are written one by one in order corresponding to number and separated by single '0' character.
Though Polycarp learnt how to encode the numbers, he has no idea how to decode them back.
 Help him calculate the decoded number.

Input
The first line contains one integer number n (1 ≤ n ≤ 89) — length of the string s.

The second line contains string s — sequence of '0' and '1' characters, number in its encoded format.
 It is guaranteed that the number corresponding to the string is positive and doesn't exceed 109.
 The string always starts with '1'.

Output
Print the decoded number.

Examples
input
3
111
output
3
input
9
110011101
output
2031

